

CONTACT



7304 Riverchase Trail Denton, Texas 76210



kristi.a.taylor@me.com



www.taylorkristi.github.io



(903) 714-0221

SKILLS

HTML/CSS

JAVASCRIPT

PYTHON

GRAPHIC DESIGN

ILLUSTRATOR

PHOTOSHOP

SOCIAL



www.linkedin.com/in/kristitaylor



github.com/taylorkristi

KRISTI TAYLOR

Front End Web Developer

ABOUT ME

I love creating functional web products that are user-centered with rock-solid code.

And I'm conscientious, fast-learner-I round out my technical skills with a unique professional background in information science. That means I understand the bigger picture, too – how design, UX, and code work together to create unique web experiences.

RECENT PROJECTS

2018 Denton Area Running Club Concept and Redesign -Co-developed a vibrant, secure website for this vibrant and community-driven running club from style concepts to end-product. Project is ongoing.

2018 Knob Hills Trail Race Concept and Redesign
Developed a website for annual trail race hosted by
Denton Area Running Club that includes an integrated calendar and

EDUCATION

a minimal one-page design.

2018 FRONT END DEVELOPER NANODEGREE Udacity (Google Developer Challenge Scholarship)

2013 MASTERS OF ART IN TEACHING Texas Woman's University

2009 MASTERS OF LIBRARY SCIENCE University of North Texas

2006 BACHELOR OF ARTS IN ENGLISH University of Texas at Tyler

WORK EXPERIENCE

2014 - PRESENT LEWISVILLE ISD | LIBRARY MEDIA SPECIALIST

2013 - 2014 PLANO ISD | 7TH GRADE ENGLISH TEACHER

2007 - 2013 BARNES AND NOBLE BOOKSELLERS | MANAGER